Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1958 -- 2014; UA044.001; 9.85 Linear Feet
  - Exploration Leaders Packet, 1989; UA044.001.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Student Exploration Evaluations Composite Sheets Fall, 1989; UA044.001.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Explo. Prgrm. Group List F'88, 1988; UA044.001.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Explo. Prgrm. Group List F'88, 1988; UA044.001.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - F. Trefethen report -, 1970; UA044.001.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Ex. Coll. Fact Sheet, UA044.001.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Faculty Lists/Explos., 1989; UA044.001.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Faculty Responses Xploration, 1989; UA044.001.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Fawaz Turki/Mideast Symposium, 1974; UA044.001.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - Films Contest Proposed by Catherine Stevens and New York Tufts Club, 1970; UA044.001.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Fipse Proposal - March 1986 Preliminary, UA044.001.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - Kathleen Fleming Fall '89 34 Paul Nardone X, 1989; UA044.001.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Free University Spring 1970 University of Pennsylvania, UA044.001.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Focal Programs, 1974; UA044.001.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Proposals S'72, 1972; UA044.001.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminar Fall, 1967; UA044.001.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminar Fall, 1968; UA044.001.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminar Spring, 1968; UA044.001.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminars Spring, 1969; UA044.001.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminars Fall, 1969; UA044.001.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminars S'70, 1970; UA044.001.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Seminar Leaders Sponsors Correspondance Received F'69, 1969; UA044.001.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - Fall '83 Course Desc., 1983; UA044.001.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Advising Explorations, 1983; UA044.001.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - Faculty Memos, 1987 -- 1988; UA044.001.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Advising: Exploration, 1984; UA044.001.018.00048 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Explorations, 1984; UA044.001.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Exploration Fall, 1986; UA044.001.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - Freshman - Explorations (by group) address List F.'88, 1988; UA044.001.018.00051 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Orientation, Fall, 1984; UA044.001.018.00052 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Orientation - Fall '86, 1986; UA044.001.018.00053 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Explorations, 1980; UA044.001.018.00054 (Box 18)
  - Freshman Year Program, 1971; UA044.001.018.00055 (Box 18)
  - Grants and Funding, 1968; UA044.001.018.00056 (Box 18)
  - Grants - Summer 1971 Lonnie Carton Proposal, UA044.001.018.00057 (Box 18)
  - Grants, Summer - Experimental College, Summer, 1970; UA044.001.018.00058 (Box 18)
  - Hofstra University - New College Experimental College, 1958; UA044.001.018.00059 (Box 18)
  - Huppert, Michael and O'Connell "Some Perspectives Concerning Higher Ed. 1969 at St. Benedict's and St. John's University", UA044.001.018.00060 (Box 18)
  - Indonesian Visitors June '70, 1970; UA044.001.018.00061 (Box 18)
  - Information About Other X Colleges, 1986; UA044.001.018.00062 (Box 18)
  - Info. Re Teaching: Misc., UA044.001.018.00063 (Box 18)
  - Innovations Committee, n.d., UA044.001.018.00064 (Box 18)
  - Experimental College Courses, 1968; UA044.001.018.00065 (Box 18)
  - 1981-1982 Innovative Teaching Awards, UA044.001.018.00066 (Box 18)
  - Innovative Teaching Awards FY 82/83, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.018.00067 (Box 18)
  - Integrated Studies Program, 1974; UA044.001.018.00068 (Box 18)
  - Interdepartmental Req. Transactions -Documentation FY 82/83 208130, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.018.00069 (Box 18)
  - Int'l Student Mailing, 1977; UA044.001.018.00070 (Box 18)
  - January Conference, 1977; UA044.001.018.00071 (Box 18)
  - Jazz Matls./Program, 1986; UA044.001.018.00072 (Box 18)
  - Jazz Week, 1984; UA044.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Letter Encouraging Grad Students to Apply to Teach XC Courses OLD, 1984; UA044.001.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Library Transactions FY 82/83 208130, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Letters from Students Core Program, 1978; UA044.001.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Liberal Arts Conference, 1978; UA044.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Life Experience Coorespondence, 1981; UA044.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Life Experiences Master Lists, 1977; UA044.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Life Experience Notes, Etc., 1977; UA044.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Patricia Lindau Paper on Observer, 1982; UA044.001.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - L. A. Trip, 1986; UA044.001.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Mapping, 1972; UA044.001.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Marketing Analysis, UA044.001.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Mary Washington College of U of V. Free University, 1970; UA044.001.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Mass. Communications: Misc. Bkgrnd., 1984; UA044.001.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Spring Explorations II, '87 Master File, 1987; UA044.001.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Mission Hill the Miracle of Boston (film presentation), 1982; UA044.001.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Museum School, 1971; UA044.001.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Music - Presented Under the Auspices of the Experimental College, 1968; UA044.001.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Nasson College Experimental College, 1969; UA044.001.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - New York, 1985; UA044.001.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - NYC Trip, 1985; UA044.001.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - NYC Trip, 1985; UA044.001.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1975; UA044.001.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Notables, UA044.001.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Ohio University - Cutler Program Experimental College, 1968; UA044.001.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Old Course Lists, 1984; UA044.001.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Old Course - Selection Mat'ls Ex. Coll. Board, 1983; UA044.001.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Old Explo. Mat'ls, 1982; UA044.001.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Old FAS, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.001.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Old job descriptions, 1976; UA044.001.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Overall Schedule (Daily Activities), 1978; UA044.001.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Old Subcomm Mat'ls, 1983; UA044.001.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - Old Telephone Charges, 1983; UA044.001.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - Orientation, Fall, 1985; UA044.001.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - Orientation, 1987; UA044.001.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - Orientation Guide, Fall, 1987; UA044.001.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - Orientation Packet Fall 1988 Kate McCaffrey Administrative Intern, UA044.001.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - Other Schools, 1962 -- 1963; UA044.001.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - Palubinskas Report of Freshman Seminar Program, Spring, 1968; UA044.001.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - Parents Weekend, 1977; UA044.001.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - FY 83/84 Personnel Doc's VL's, 1983 -- 1984; UA044.001.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - Perspectives, F, 1988; UA044.001.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - Inactive Perspectives, Fall, 1989; UA044.001.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - Perspectives Composites, F, 1989; UA044.001.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - Perspectives Leaders Evaluations, Fall, 1989; UA044.001.019.00045 (Box 19)
  - Perspectives Reccomendations Leaders Never Followed Through, 1989; UA044.001.019.00046 (Box 19)
  - Petty Cash Documentation FY 82/83 208130 and Reciepts, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.019.00047 (Box 19)
  - Planning/Management, UA044.001.019.00048 (Box 19)
  - Population Course, 1986; UA044.001.019.00049 (Box 19)
  - Population Budgeting, 1986; UA044.001.019.00050 (Box 19)
  - Pre-Freshman, 1965; UA044.001.019.00051 (Box 19)
  - Proposal F'65 Core Seminar Satisfying Selected Foundation Requirements, 1965; UA044.001.019.00052 (Box 19)
  - Proposal July 26, 1966 Freshman Year Program, UA044.001.019.00053 (Box 19)
  - Purchasing Reg. Transactions - Documentations FY 82/83 208130, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.019.00054 (Box 19)
  - 208130 - Reciepts, 1983; UA044.001.019.00055 (Box 19)
  - Religion 55 Death and Dying, UA044.001.019.00056 (Box 19)
  - Reports and Memos, 1969; UA044.001.019.00057 (Box 19)
  - Reports and Memos, 1976; UA044.001.019.00058 (Box 19)
  - Reply from Chairman Experimental College Committee, 1983; UA044.001.019.00059 (Box 19)
  - Reports and Memos, 1968; UA044.001.019.00060 (Box 19)
  - Reports and Memos (1970), UA044.001.019.00061 (Box 19)
  - Robyn's Correspondence, 1975; UA044.001.019.00062 (Box 19)
  - Robyn's Correspondence, 1977 -- 1978; UA044.001.019.00063 (Box 19)
  - Robyn's Correspondence, 1976 -- 1977; UA044.001.019.00064 (Box 19)
  - Robyn's Correspondence, 1973 -- 1974; UA044.001.019.00065 (Box 19)
  - Rossman, Michael 1968 "On Learning and Social Change", UA044.001.019.00066 (Box 19)
  - Rossman, Michael "Prospects for Radical Ed. Reform Within the System", UA044.001.019.00067 (Box 19)
  - SAIL, 1986; UA044.001.019.00068 (Box 19)
  - Seminar Attendance Sheets, UA044.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Seminar Handouts F, 1986; UA044.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Seminar to Initiate New Experiments in Undergraduate Education, 1965; UA044.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Senior Seminar, 1980; UA044.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Short Term Studies Program, 1980; UA044.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Sommerville: General Community Reports, 1973; UA044.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Amy Stein SSP S, 1984; UA044.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Students A-G, UA044.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Students H-Z, UA044.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Student Sabbatical, 1968; UA044.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Subcomm Review Process, 1984; UA044.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Summer 84 Notes, 1984; UA044.001.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Summer School, 1968; UA044.001.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - Summer School, 1978; UA044.001.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - TA Working File, 1983; UA044.001.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Teaching Asst Matl's, 1984; UA044.001.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - TA Orientation OLD, 1984; UA044.001.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - TA Orientation, 1983; UA044.001.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - Teacher Replies Evaluations, 1973; UA044.001.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - TUTV: Tufts University Television, 1981; UA044.001.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - University Committee Student and Faculty Lont-Range Planning, 1968; UA044.001.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - University Curriculum - X Coll. Suggestions, 1973; UA044.001.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - Unsolicited Letters, Vitae, Etc. "With the Wrong Idea", 1982; UA044.001.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - Upperclassmen: Lead a Frosh. Seminar, 1968; UA044.001.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - V.L. Personnel, 1984 -- 1985; UA044.001.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - Personal Documents (PCA's Etc.) FY, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - Visiting Lecturer, 1975 -- 1976; UA044.001.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - Washington D.C., 1985; UA044.001.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - Washington D.C., 1987; UA044.001.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - Winter Study, 1973; UA044.001.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - WMFO Radio, 1978; UA044.001.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - XC Personnel Corr and Notes and Miscellany, 1981 -- 1982; UA044.001.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - XC Budget Matl's Miscellaneous (Some 82/83 - Some Older Records), 1982 -- 1983; UA044.001.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - Year End Evaluation - '72 and Survey, 1972 -- 1973; UA044.001.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - Beyond the Barricades, 1969-1970(:) A Forum on the Legacies of Campus Activism, UA044.001.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - Research for Ex-Coll bio and 25th anniversary, circa 1988 -- 1999; UA044.001962 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Research for Ex-Coll bio and 25th anniversary, circa 1989; UA044.001963 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Mieckelejohn Education Foundation and Wilderness Convocation, circa 1989 -- 1990; UA044.001964; 2 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 24-25)
  - Experimental College correspondence and courses, 1965; UA044.001965 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Experimental College correspondence and courses, 1966 -- 1968; UA044.001966 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Experimental College correspondence and courses, 1969; UA044.001967 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Experimental College correspondence and courses, 1970; UA044.001968 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Experimental College correspondence and courses, 1962 -- 1964; UA044.001969 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Experimental College establishment, 1962 -- 1964; UA044.001970 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Experimental College minutes, 1964 -- 1969 Feburary; UA044.001971 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Leave of absence, alternatives, circa 1984; UA044.001972 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Experimental College newsletter, circa 1986 -- 1987; UA044.001973 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Experimental College Peace and Social Justice Program Peace and Justice News, circa 1986 -- 1987; UA044.001974 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Experimental College programs and proposals, 1964 -- 1966; UA044.001975 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Experimental College programs and proposals, 1967 -- 1973; UA044.001976 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Experimental College handouts, circa 1993 -- 2004; UA044.001977 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - List of courses and instructors, 1974 -- 1975; UA044.001978 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Experimental College reports, 1965 -- 1974; UA044.001979 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Ex-College celebrating 50 years, circa 2014; UA044.001980 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Experimental College handout, circa 2012; UA044.001981 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Explorations and Perspectives, 1967 -- 2000; UA044.002; 6.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains the Explorations and Perspectives course folders. The Explorations and Perspectives are freshman seminar classes. They are student taught with faculty advisers who may choose to sit in on the classes. They are created to help freshman students adjust to the academic and social life of the university. The course name and each instructors name is recorded for each course. Course folders may include class lists, syllabi, reading lists, course descriptions, and student evaluations of the course. Explorations (courses numbered EXP009) are topics developed by the students and approved by the Experimental College. Students develop the course curriculum. The theme of Perspectives (courses numbered EXP 008) is set by the Experimental College each year. The student instructors are responsible for developing the individual section's curriculum within that framework. Prior to 1971 all courses of this type were called "Freshman Seminars."
  This series is arranged chronologically by semester.
  Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
  - Explorations F, 1973; UA044.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Evaluations F, 1973; UA044.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Fall, 1974; UA044.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Exploration Evaluation, 1974; UA044.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Explorations, 1975; UA044.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Explorations F, 1975; UA044.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Explorations F, 1976; UA044.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Explorations, 1976; UA044.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Colloquia, 1976 -- 1977; UA044.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Freshmen Explorations, 1977; UA044.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Fall, 1977; UA044.002.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - QUIDNUNCS, 1977; UA044.002.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Explorations F, 1975; UA044.002.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Explorations, 1978; UA044.002.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Explorations F, 1979; UA044.002.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Fall, 1979; UA044.002.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Explorations F, 1980; UA044.002.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Spring 1980 All Information/Evaluations, UA044.002.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Spring, 1981; UA044.002.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Explorations Evaluations Fall, 1981; UA044.002.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Fall 1981 Exploration, UA044.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Explorations Spring, 1982; UA044.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Explorations Fall, 1982; UA044.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Curriculum Review - Interim Report to the Faculty November, 1992; UA044.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - 9W Morality, Immorality & Amorality Freshman Seminar, 1967 -- 1968; UA044.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Explorations Spring, 1983; UA044.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Explorations Fall, 1983; UA044.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Explorations, Fall, 1983; UA044.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - January '84 Explorations, 1984; UA044.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Explorations S, 1984; UA044.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Explorations Fall, 1984; UA044.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Explorations F, 1984; UA044.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Handouts in Explor Leader Seminars Fall, 1984; UA044.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Attendance - Fall, 1984; UA044.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Exploration Lists (Masters) F, 1984; UA044.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Spring 1985 Exploration Program, UA044.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Explorations II A Spring, 1985; UA044.002.005.00017; Levey, Douglas; Shapiro, Loren (Box 5)
  - Explorations II B Spring, 1985; UA044.002.005.00018; Furkart, Audrey; Price, Barbara; Ordway, Abigail (Box 5)
  - Explorations II C Spring, 1985; UA044.002.005.00019; Pincus, Laura; DeBroff, Brian; Jacobs, Steve (Box 5)
  - Explorations II D Spring, 1985; UA044.002.005.00020; Holland, Stacy; Covall, Lisa (Box 5)
  - Explorations II -- Spring, 1985; UA044.002.005.00021; Mancini, Linda; Seasholes, Brad (Box 5)
  - South Africa -- Divestment May 2, 1985; UA044.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - 1985 - Exploration Leaders Handouts - Sample Packet, UA044.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Handouts to Fall 85 Explorations Leaders, 1985; UA044.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Fall '85 Explorations Mailing Matrixes, 1985; UA044.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Attendance Fall, 1985; UA044.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - EXP 009 A: Ice Breakers, 1985; UA044.002.005.00027; Black, Caren; Schorr, Denise (Box 5)
  - Explorations - Advisors, 1985; UA044.002.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - EXP 009 B: Tufts: One Milestone in a Dynamic World, 1985; UA044.002.005.00029; Brous, Nils; Mogavero, Matthew; Siskind, Adam (Box 5)
  - EXP 009 C: Racism, Homophobia, Inter-Religious Relat., 1985; UA044.002.005.00030; Wint, Saadia; Loftis, David (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 D: This is Your Life, 1985; UA044.002.005.00031; Last, John; Daley, Miriam (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 E: Vegetable - Not Just a State of Mind, 1985; UA044.002.005.00032; Lessler, Amy; Guilbeault, Grant (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 F: Health in the 80's, 1985; UA044.002.005.00033; Spiegel, Nina; Mettel, Kenny; Moslow, Jeff (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 G: Stress and Ordinary People, 1985; UA044.002.005.00034; McEwen, Carolyn; Tarver, Hal; Thorgerson, Lisa (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 H: Fighting the Freshman, 1985; UA044.002.005.00035; Fenton, Sherlyn; Yarckin, Wendy; Rosenfeld, Dan (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 J: Sex, Drugs, & Rock 'n' Roll, 1985; UA044.002.005.00036; Feinberg, Susan; Haffer, Beth; Sigman, Scott (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 K: Flying High, 1985; UA044.002.005.00037; Hofmann, Donnagene; Weitzner, Wendy; Lord, Stephen (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 L: From Draft Cards to Gold Cards -- Youth Culture, 1985; UA044.002.005.00038; Murphy, Mary; Roby, Jennifer; O'Leary, Kevin (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 M: Talk of the Town, 1985; UA044.002.005.00039; Koobatian, Thomas; Levy, Alyssa; Scaramucci, Anthony (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 N: Around the World in ABC's, 1985; UA044.002.005.00040; Oettinger, Julie; Kosson, Ellie; Ross, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 P: I Love It When You Call Me Names, 1985; UA044.002.005.00041; Foreman, Terri; Formisano, Gina; Suarez, J.P. (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 Q: From Ward Cleever to Blake Carrington, 1985; UA044.002.005.00042; Cook, Julie; Pearlstein, Mark; Shapiro, Randy (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 R: American Advertising, 1985; UA044.002.005.00043; Stewart, Elizabeth; Van Raalte, Judy (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 S: Big Games Played In Court, 1985; UA044.002.005.00044; Cloherty, Kevin; Friedman, Robert; Salloway, Leslie (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 T: The Devil Made Me Do It, 1985; UA044.002.005.00045; Cohen, Elaine; Simowitz, Randi (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 U: American Outlaws, 1985; UA044.002.005.00046; Banburg, Anthony; Philips, Andrea; Van Slyck, Virginia (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 V: Baseball, Hotdogs, Apple II, 1985; UA044.002.005.00047; Cook, Lisa; Benveniste, Dianne (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 W:Decisions, Decisions, 1985; UA044.002.005.00048; Miller, Heidi; Weene, Michelle; Robinson, David (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 X: Groups, Groups And More..., 1985; UA044.002.005.00049; Hoffner, Paul; Newman, Stephen; Szulman, Doug (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 Y: Theories of the Couch, 1985; UA044.002.005.00050; Bennett, Douglas; Giarusso, Lisa; Potsdam, Eric (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 Z: I'm O.K. ... You're a Witch, 1985; UA044.002.005.00051; Gochman, Janet; Gomez, Alyce; Kerman, Ben (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 AA: Hightech in America, 1985; UA044.002.005.00052; Enright, Malia; McHugh, Michael (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 BB: Finance For The Fun Of It, 1985; UA044.002.005.00053; Hotch, Jeffrey; Pearlman, Steven; Roth, Lori (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 CC: Looking Forward To, 1985; UA044.002.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 DD: Reading Between the Lines, 1985; UA044.002.005.00055; Copen, Rob; Petricone, Michael (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 EE: As the World Turns, 1985; UA044.002.005.00056; Bree, Adam; Wiley, Laura (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 FF: The Unfolding Lotus, 1985; UA044.002.005.00057; Brodsky, Bari-Sue; Moran, Peter (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 GG: Scandinavia at a Glance, 1985; UA044.002.005.00058; Kim, Donald; Leftkowitz, Karen (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 HH: From Stalin To Stolichnaya, 1985; UA044.002.005.00059; Capobianco, Stacy; Spungin, Debra; Jennings, Donald (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 JJ: Over the Borderline, 1985; UA044.002.005.00060; Davila, Arlene; Hansen, Regina; Liang, Li-ching (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 KK: Whodunit?, 1985; UA044.002.005.00061; Scali, Marisa; Sude, Laurie; Viscosi, Valerie (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 LL: A Half-Hour of Laughs, 1985; UA044.002.005.00062; Herbsman, Jonas; Kram, Derek; Wolpert, Ivan (Box 5)
  - Exp 009 MM: Deeper Than Popcorn, 1985; UA044.002.006.00001; Brog, Tim; Matluck, Susan Rose; Sakin, Sheri (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 NN: Cinema, Culture, and Youth, 1985; UA044.002.006.00002; Casalduc, Leticia; Cutro, James; Friedman, Dave (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 PP: American Film Heroes, 1985; UA044.002.006.00003; Keusch, Larry; Kursman, Scott; Winters, Richard (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 QQ: American Film Genres, 1985; UA044.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 RR: The Critic's Eye, 1985; UA044.002.006.00005; Murphy, Paul; Varon, Elana (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 SS: The Play's the Thing, 1985; UA044.002.006.00006; Milavskas, Brian; Sampson, Paul (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 TT:Just For Laughs, 1985; UA044.002.006.00007; Koty, Richard; Glou, Karen; Luchsinger, Bruce (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 VV: The Art of Comedy and Laughter, 1985; UA044.002.006.00008; Cohen, Sherri; Hurwitz, Andy; Stamato, Liz (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 UU: That's Not Funny, That's Sick, 1985; UA044.002.006.00009; Atlas, David; Zipes, Debbie (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 WW: From the Top of the Hub..., 1985; UA044.002.006.00010; Heller, Kathy; Mayer, Sandra (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 XX: Bean Town - The Frank Story, 1985; UA044.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 YY: The Culture of the City, 1985; UA044.002.006.00012; Monjo, Rolf; Rigby, Rebecca (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 ZZ: From Brahmins to Beans, 1985; UA044.002.006.00013; Kaplan, Lauren; Stearns, Dana (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 AAA: Boston And From Whence It Came, 1985; UA044.002.006.00014; Abedon, Todd; Rothenburger, Kristin; Talmo, Evelyn (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 BBB: Experience The Best Of Boston, 1985; UA044.002.006.00015; Murstein, Andrew; Sussman, Michele; Walden, David (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 CCC: Boston- The Metamorphoses Of A City, 1985; UA044.002.006.00016; Goodman, Julie; Penotti, John (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 DDD: George Orwell, 1985; UA044.002.006.00017; Keller, John; Kleeger, Jeff; Rappaport, Jennifer (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 EEE: Action/Reaction, 1985; UA044.002.006.00018; Criss, David; Berman, Gary; Silverman, Sue (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 K: Conflict in the 80's, 1987; UA044.002.006.00019; Simon, Andrew G.; Creem, Stacey; Singer, John David (Box 6)
  - Exp 009 EE: Ethnicity in American Culture, 1990; UA044.002.006.00020; Freedman, Matthew; Jones, William L. (Box 6)
  - "The Voice Of America" Exploration, 1983; UA044.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Experiencing Films Exploration Spring, 1986; UA044.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - "Meet the Press" Freshman Exploration Fall, 1984; UA044.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Freshman Exploration, 1983; UA044.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Freshman Exploration, 1985; UA044.002.006.00025 (Box 6)